(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-02T00:10:29.252080",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
[Mori Calliope 5th Anniversary Show: The Story Thus Far]
みなさん...
Everyone...
I don't feel so good.
Feel like I'm gonna collapse... some sickness...
Like I just went through a freaking...
portal, or... something crazy just happened.
At least I can see chat. Howdy.
Or dead... No, I'm okay.
Don't you worry about me. I'm... I'm fine.
There's... There's a lot of Dead Beats here today.
Maybe Dead Beats, KF members, Takodachis, there's a lot of...
people.
Let me catch my breath for a minute here.
Hold on.
That was some crazy traveling that I just did.
I think I went through like a... a wormhole or something.
It's not my fault that my eyes are done—
No, hey, wait a minute.
Hey...
If you start glitching... if it's stuff like that, I swear to God, I'll beat you...
...within an inch of your life.
It's fine.
We're supposed to celebrate my fifth anniversary... I'm five!
Can you guys believe I'm five?
Hold on, I probably should adjust the camera a little bit. You can't...
...see me. Hang on.
Oh, you know what? I think I can take control of it if I click... there we go.
Oh.
Hey there!
What's up?
What do you... what do you think?
Do you like it? You like this new outfit I found myself in?
"You look cute." Thank you. Um, a lot of the girls told me I look like a robber, which...
...now that I've said it, you guys, you know, might, might be able to see it.
But, you know, there there are various things that I can do and and change with this, so...
So...
"Beautiful." Oh, thank you. "You look amazing." Thank you very much! "Nice outfit," they say.
I'm I'm glad that you like it. There's there's many things that I can do...
...um...
...but I feel like I should— You know, a good magician never shows all of their tricks like right away, you know?
So, I figure we have lots of time to celebrate...
...what is essentially five years of all of us being together, right?
So, I feel like I should be a little happier about that, right? Thankfully, I can do something about that.
Yay! Five years! Five years!
But, you know, as as you guys know, your Mori has like a little bit of a resting B-word face,
...so I kind of... kind of have to force myself to smile a little bit. That's okay, I I can do that.
I can totally do that.
Heh.
Oh, wait, sorry, I grabbed you. I didn't mean to grab you.
What if I...
Peace.
There.
Tehe-pero-pero.
Hold on, I I can do more than that though. That's not... I'm not a one-trick pony or anything.
Raar!
This is my favorite face ever!
Cuz this is... this is how I look all the time off-stream when you don't see me.
It's like I I click "stream owari" and then my eyes just immediately shrink to look like this.
Just, just so you know, this is... this is my usual, this is my normal, my nature.
So shocked.
Uh, shock is one word for it. Uh, Dead Beats and Ghost Cats see this every day, you're right.
You're right, Dead Beats. This is... this is the Mommy that they're used to.
And then this is just my current, my... my constant state of being.
You guys don't mind, right?
Resting B-word face.
No problem, no problem.
Hi.
No, you guys are... you guys, I'm just tired, but I'm I'm happy.
I'm happy but I'm tired. This is... this is normal, this is usual.
Nope, it's all good.
But but someday, um, we have plans to get like some some really good, very decent...
...face tracking, so look forward to that.
Um, oh by the way, just really quick, before before we get too in-deep into this,
...um, I have an announcement. There's a special goodie available to you guys.
You guys like goodies? I like goodies. You guys like goodies?
Um, we have... we have a very special item for those of you that use VR Chat.
It is a penlight...
...for this specific event that you'll be able to claim.
There's gonna be a link in the description, they're updating it as we speak.
Um, and also there will be a link on... Twitter,
...Twitter, uh, for you guys to grab it. It's very special, it's got the logo from this specific event,
and I I wanted to put it out there, um, thankfully with the help, um, of AEV and, ... and...
and I I wanted to put it out there, um, thankfully with the help, um, of AEV and, um, and...
...and VR Chat, uh, to do something really special for you guys.
This is a claimable item just to celebrate this... this big event together with you guys.
I hope you guys will enjoy it and use it in VR Chat, and have lots of fun with your friends.
If we ever do something like... future concerts in VR Chat, I'm I'm always really open to like...
...figuring out new tech and stuff like that, uh, together with, you know, the other members,
and all these really amazing technically powerful, uh, folks, and figure out like what more...
...cool creative stuff we can do together in terms of like... lives and whatnot, cuz like for example...
...this amazing world that we're gonna go explore.
Oh man, it's nostalgic.
It's nostalgic.
Um, I want to do more fun stuff like this.
...is what I've realized after working so hard on this project for so long.
So, um...
So, yeah!
Uh, thanks for... for being a part of it though, you guys.
I feel like I can get even wackier.
Hold on, expressions. Face... face expression. Hold on.
Slay.
Wah!
This is not a me you get to see very often.
Aha!
And there's also...
...constantly sleepy. Is this... is this, too, is Sinnsky?
My beloved. Now I look like her.
Um, we... we should move along. I know that we should move along.
First, I want to give a really huge thank you to...
...two folks who made this outfit possible.
Thank you so much to...
...the designer of this outfit, Nanoliss!
You guys know Nanoliss?
Nanoliss is so amazing, and just has the most beautiful designs ever, outfit designs.
And, uh, I had wanted to work with Nano for the longest time.
So, I'm so glad that I got this outfit fully designed by Nanoliss.
Hopefully... we we might get... we might get like a, uh, reference image at some point.
But thank you so much to Nano for creating this outfit.
I love it so dearly! I want to use it in music videos.
Um, so please look forward to... to that in the future.
And I also want to give a big ups to Yuli, as well, who designed the model for this outfit...
...did all the 3D modeling for it.
So Nanoliss did the design and Yuli did the actual 3D modeling...
...and neither of those are easy tasks at all.
Um, so thank you for going out of your way to make time for...
...just a little, a little five-year-old Reaper like me.
I say five, I'm actually 90 years old, but you get... you get the point.
It's been five years together, right?
Um, but yay! Yuli's so... so goated, Nano's so goated. Thank you so much!
And of course, this world...
We're gonna get a little bit more into the creation of this world as well, I think.
But before we do that, we got to kind of... I want to kind of explore a little bit.
You know, there's stuff to look at around here, you guys. Hold on.
Did... did you guys see... Hey, hang on a second. There are a bunch of signs around here.
My Reaper looking extra cute. Thank you! Your Reaper is...
...is trying to figure out where the heck we are, but there are some clues...
...here and there that we can look at, right? So let's take a look at this.
Ooh.
I can read.
Due to a thanatological... thanatological... I know...
I know Thanatos! That's a... That's a Persona.
Uh, due to a thanatological... I know... I know that means death.
It's like Latin or... something like that, I don't know.
The thanatological incident, the elevator is out of service.
Whether you are alive or dead, please seek out your local psychopomp.
I know a couple psychopomps.
None of them are in Holo, but maybe someday we'll get a psychopomp.
I feel like we'd be really good friends and get along.
I don't know, five years I've been here we haven't had a psychopomp, but who knows in the next five.
We could maybe welcome one.
That would be cool.
Ame's elevator? See, that's what I'm thinking.
I remember this elevator, even just from the shape of it, right?
Do not annoy the...
elevator attendant Ame.
Yeah, no, this is... This is definitely...
...This is 100% Ame's elevator, I think.
What happened to it?
You guys know what the heck happened to this place?
Maximum capacity: 12 people. 50 if smol.
Do you guys remember when we had less than 12 people?
'Cause I do. I remember when we had less than 12.
Look at that. Then, not everybody would have been able to fit...
...into the elevator. You know, what about...
...What about, um, Advent and Justice, right? They wouldn't be able to fit.
Um, I mean, they could if they were smol.
But... The elevator would need to be renovated so that we could all fit.
Ame... Ame elevator.
Back then...
Smol... Long times, yeah, yeah. The time has flown by so fast, says chat.
Mhm, mhm. Time flies when you're having fun, right guys?
Uh, let's see. Do not fall...
...into the time vortex.
We don't know what will happen, but it doesn't look good.
Okay, gonna heed those wise words.
Strong quantum fluctuations, keep yourself observed at all times to avoid disappearing.
What the heck? I don't want to disappear, I have stuff to do!
Speaking of stuff to do, maybe we should...
...maybe we should move right along, um, because there are some really cool spots around here, and I think I see...
Don't get too excited. Oh gosh, sorry!
I really shook you around a little bit. Let me... I don't mean to do that.
Do not get too excited. But, I think I saw...
Get this, Dead Beats.
A resort.
Will Mori Calliope be going there?
Probably, probab—
Yes, I will for the sake of...
For the sake of this journey.
We'll go to the resort.
You guys want to come with? Better not go alone.
So my Dead Beats got to come with me, okay?
You guys got to come with me. Is that all right?
You guys cool with that?
All right.
I could kind of use a rest.
It would be nice.
We got some fun surprises today,
so please look forward to them.
But I guess we'll try and make our way
out of here then, shall we?
Mm, let's do it.
"We need to observe you to prevent a disappearance."
You make a good point, skeletons. You do.
Well, let's go ahead and head on over then, shall we?
What does this say? Hub...
Oh, I can't— Sorry, chat's in my way. That's alright.
I want you guys here. I want you...
I want you here, so...
It's no problem. "Hub area," it says.
Okay.
Observing. They're observing right now. Okay.
Mane-chans, hear that? Also, Mane-chans are here...
...working as hard as possible with cameras. Thank you.
All right. Well, I guess off we go!
To the resort. Oh, gosh.
I don't like going to resorts because I feel like...
...I'm gonna give in to my base human instincts,
instead of my Reaper side,
which says, "Work, work, work."
My human side says it's time for a vacation.
So, let's... Let's just go.
We'll just go and see what happens, you know?
Making my way uptown.
Whoa!
I really need to fix my posture!
No, it's— It's fine. Go ahead.
My posture's not the best.
And I can walk on water, by the way, in case...
In case you didn't know. You like my Naruto run?
It's just my current state of being.
And we're back.
Oh wait, did you guys see the design on my back?
The skull? That's my logo!
I really want to release this jacket someday.
Wouldn't that be cool? It'd be cool merch.
I feel like I release too many clothing items, though.
We really don't need that many.
Well, anyway, I guess we'd better...
...better get out of here. Uh...
What am I looking at? Gosh, don't want to show you...
...what the clothes can do yet.
We'll get to that later, shall we?
Okay.
Let us be on our way,
up the stairs. I'll try to...
My posture's great!
I never would bend my back while I walk.
That's not something Mori Calliope would ever do.
Whoa!
You guys see this?
This is a full-blown resort. What's— Hold on.
Hey, what's this switch here? It's got a camera.
Can I activate it, I wonder? Oh!
Wow! Check it!
You guys get a sweeping view.
Nice perspective! "Anything wrong with your spine?"
No, it needs relaxation. That's why we're here.
It looks like I could run around it like a Dark Souls map.
Not everything is Dark Souls, so just, you know—
There's a bar!
Wait, hold on, I just barely missed... Fix my knee.
Dead Beats...
...hold on, we're in trouble now.
Hang on, let's get to the center here. Wow!
I don't look very enthused, but I am excited.
Booze! No, wait a minute, Dead Beats, not yet.
It's not time, we have to...
Bar Mori!
Do you guys remember Bar Mori? Because I do.
Oh, that was so fun.
Loved Bar Mori. We should've had more adventures.
But that's on me, got too busy with other stuff.
My knee's been feeling tired these days... my knee.
There we go.
Anyway...
...fancy, classic.
This is not VR Chat, this is a vlog on Calli's vacation.
Wait, no, you got it all wrong! You got—
I'm— I'm working hard, I promise!
Look at the way the water reflects off of me, though.
Isn't it pretty neat?
Hold on, can I do peace?
Peace.
I'm doing a pose, I'm doing a po— Peace.
Hope you guys get lots of screenshots. Remember...
...to use #5YearsOfMori...
...to share your favorite screenshots, okay?
#5YearsOfMori. You can also share memories...
...or, you know, fan art too, whatever you want.
#5YearsOfMori to celebrate five years...
...of the Grim Reaper invading your personal space.
And by personal, I mean like your home.
You know, cause when you watch me, I'm there.
Well, I guess we should look around a little more.
Cool. Whoa, what's this?
Yes...
I dare not.
I dare not lay down.
We don't have time for that. We don't have time.
Let's, let's get moving around a little bit...
...because we got stuff to do.
Hang on a sec. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yagoo?
Hey, there's a bar over there, though.
There's a bar, but before we get to Yagoo...
...can we just, can we hit the bar really quick?
Hang on.
No, this is...
...this is big. This is big, big news.
All right, Dead Beats.
Welcome to Bar Mori.
Welcome to Bar Mori... Oh, you guys are back here.
I wonder if I can... Let me get a martini, wait.
Hang on, I'm pulling you over here.
I'm pulling my chat in front of my face...
...so that I can, I can see them. Okay.
Pop, float, and... Okay, there we go.
Now I can see you perfectly.
Now I can, I can take your order. What would you guys like?
Can I get some whiskey?
Yes, I actually... I saved some just for this special occasion, so...
...uh, let me go grab it. Right here.
Yes, welcome to Bar Mori. Here it is.
Hold, hold to grab... oh, this one.
Hold to grab... oh, this.
Okay, I got it.
No, I...
Wait, I dropped it! Okay, hold on, hold on...
I'm not very good at this.
Maybe I really do need a vacation.
Wait, no, okay, hang on.
The melon soda? See, that's, that's a good choice.
All right, here's...
Any glasses here? We don't, um...
Well, all right, chat. This is for you.
Fetch!
It landed perfectly upright!
It landed perfectly!
You know what? This reminds me. I used to tell you guys about my...
...my old job.
I used to have a tough, old job...
...that I did back in the day.
And I...
...I served somebody a drink that didn't have enough...
...like, vodka or tequila in it, and they threw it in my face.
I remember telling you guys about that.
Well, I've been through a lot...
...and I'm ready to unleash my rage!
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Something happened.
Okay, sorry, I had a blackout right there for a second.
All right, is this Amaretto?
Can I juggle it?
Yeah, I can.
Oh, man, she's too good.
Oh, she's too skilled... Oh, god, I dropped it!
Okay, it's cuz I got cocky.
It happens all the time for me.
Uh, hang on, I got it. No problem.
"So talented," they say. Big ups!
What do you mean, no, no, there's no "Endou".
Stop, chigau yo!
Coming out of your paycheck.
You know what I think about that?
I may have thrown it too far.
Oh, there it goes!
Hey, this is way, this is better than I thought.
Whoa, this is actually very stress-relieving...
...believe it or not.
Yeah, sometimes you just feel like you gotta...
I was supposed to be serving the Dead Beats.
Is this the thanks that they get after five years of being loyal supporters...
...of the Grim Reaper? You know what? Yes, it is.
That's messed up.
I have other goodies. I have other...
...other goodies for you guys, I promise.
Yes, yes it is. It's so worth it. You guys are too kind to me.
The Dead Beats are the kindest, what the heck.
What do you... No, no, chigau, chigau, chigau!
There's no...
Forget your street fights...
...this a trench war. Hang on, can I pick up the...
Oh my... I can pick up everything!
They freaking killed it with this. Who is "they"?
I will tell you shortly.
But...
...anyway, we could play with, I could throw bottles at you guys all day.
But we do have to move right along because we got schedule to keep.
Schedule to keep.
All right, let's go check out what the heck happened over here.
Um, what am I looking at?
That's, uh... That's real special.
Right over there, the Yagoo. I want to see...
...if I can pull you guys up before me again, get in front of my face.
But yeah, so you can see. Hang on.
I got you.
Now, don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid, my small lambs. This man will not hurt you.
He's just...
...he just has really expensive shorts.
That's, uh, that's my boss, by the way. Michelangelo's Yagoo.
Golden swim trunks, actually.
Uh, 24k gold swim trunks on my boss.
Good for him. Good for him.
Thank you for, thank you for, uh, the, the resort resources.
Hey, is that Justice?
Cool! We also have paintings of my cute kohai as well here.
Very nice.
And then the architecture... Whoa! Okay, we're not that ancient.
Yo, who made this?
Who made this Myth...?
Well, I don't know. What do you guys think?
Ancient Myth!
Oh man, this is where my membership money goes, Dead Beats, right?
It sure is, right, right here.
It's a, a grand carving such as this.
It's a grand carving such as this.
Myth.
Yes, the, the oldest and most decrepit and most ancient.
Yes, the oldest, most decrepit, and most ancient.
After that, we moved into the, the Promise Age.
After that, we moved into the Promise Age.
I Promise! Cute!
I love that this one is different in that it looks like it could be a kindergartener's drawing,
but it's clearly not. Like, they made it with intent.
So, it's not... it's not really what it is, but...
Anyway, let's go, Promise!
And then we also have, oh, we can't forget them, Ad- Advent right here!
And then we also have, oh, we can't forget them, Advent right here!
There's Advent.
Look at all my cute kouhai.
Look at all my cute juniors.
Solidified in history!
What a place of beautiful art.
There's a lot of artisticness that went into this, a lot of artistry.
Oh man, we got to, we got to give thanks though, to whoever put all of this together, right?
Oh man, we've got to give thanks though, to whoever put all of this together, right?
Shall we go take a quick look?
Here we go.
This map was created by SeafoamBoy.
Map design and concept art and modeling.
Map design, concept art, and modeling.
And then, Mmaellon, programming and camera systems.
Wow, why... why are we looking at this plaque like they're dead or something? Did they die?
I don't think that they died or anything like that.
They did so well, though.
I mean, Seafoam's, Seafoam's vision here is just so amazing.
I mean, Seafoam's vision here is just so amazing.
I can see there's so much nostalgia and love for the five years
that HoloEN has been together like this.
I think it's such a cool concept,
and I'm so excited to share all of this with you guys.
It's so, so cool!
Probably one of the coolest things I've ever done in those five years
is get a place like this,
is getting a place like this,
get to visit a place like this, right?
getting to visit a place like this, right?
And then of course we can't forget Mmaellon who has helped so much
with the programming and the camera systems.
I mean, the camera system's my favorite part of this whole thing.
I mean, the camera system is my favorite part of this whole thing.
Like, normally you can't do all this crazy stuff with cameras, but
I am so, so, so grateful!
Oh, thank you so much to you guys for the help!
And all the programming, too. Man, I, my brain is...
And all the programming, too. Man, my brain is...
You guys know how my brain is. It's not capable of handling things that programmer brain can handle, so
You guys know how my brain is. It's not capable of handling things that a programmer brain can handle, so
I really, I really appreciate it.
And I'm so excited!
I don't look like I'm excited, but I'm excited to get to the rest of it.
So, yay!
We know, hey, hold on a second.
Well, it's okay, I invited that conversation, so.
But, there's something I want to... there's something that's been bugging me,
Dead Beats, while we've been here.
It's that I feel like I did something here already.
I feel like I have a memory of...
being here
at a different time.
And I'm not just talking about the fact that it reminds me of the original Myth lobby in many ways.
But oh, wow, I really did just drop drinks everywhere, huh? Okay.
That's kind of messed up.
I really shouldn't have done that. That was very rude of me.
I feel as though I've... I've sung a song here before
with friends.
Um...
And I want, I'm thinking I might end up remembering that.
And I'm thinking I might end up remembering that.
I think I sung a couple of songs here.
And so,
I think I want to
flashback to those if I can.
I feel like if I channel like my inner, my innermost mind,
I feel like if I channel my inner... my innermost mind,
my inner brain,
then I can have like a "That's So Raven" moment,
where like you gaze into the future, but instead it's the past.
where you gaze into the future, but instead it's the past.
You think life will be a breeze...
Sorry, sorry.
Anyway, so let's... let's do that, everybody.
Let's...
Let's go!
Flashback!
on and on , it goes on and on
On and on, it goes on and on
you gotta let me go , but i 'm already gone
You gotta let me go, but I'm already gone
on and on , it goes on and on
On and on, it goes on and on
you gotta let me go
でしょ？
Right?
暗く なる 頃 始まる パーティー
The party starts when it gets dark
集まる 人種 は 々
All kinds of people gather
明日 なき 夜 に ダーク な 遊び
A dark game in a night with no tomorrow
that 's my design さあ 創造
That's my design, now create
刺激 が 欲しい
I want stimulation
命 の 限り
As long as I live
迷 える アタシ と 夜通し イイ ？
Will you spend the night with lost me?
あらあら あらあら
My, my, my, my
ホント は ずっと もう
Honestly, all this time
楽しい フリ し て
I've been pretending to have fun
消え た アタシ を
Please find me,
キミ が 見つけ て
the one who disappeared
ね ほら
See? Look!
フラフラ する でしょう
You feel lightheaded, don't you?
クラクラ 来る でしょう
You feel dizzy, don't you?
ホロホロ とろけ そう そう でしょう
About to melt, right?
flash bang
クラクラ来るでしょう
You're feeling dizzy, aren't you?
そろそろ壊れそう
Looks like you're about to break
そうでしょう
Right?
FLASH BANG
Hey! Hey! Come on!
Woo! Break it down! FLASH BANG!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Come on everybody!
FLASH BANG! Yeah, yeah. Verse two.
まどろむ underground
Slumbering underground
浮ついた開放感
A restless sense of freedom
剥がれたペルソナ
Persona stripped away
放り投げ break it down
Cast it aside, break it down
だんだん崩れてく感覚
The sensation of gradually crumbling
染まるのは息する様にカンタン
Being dyed is as easy as breathing
変わっていくアタシ 時は待ったなし
I'm changing, time waits for no one
涙を涸らし あらあらあらあら
Drying my tears, oh my, oh my...
いやぁまあなんか転生した？
Well, did I reincarnate or something?
みたいない世界感
Like an otherworldly feeling
纏って違う人みたいだ
Wrapped in it, looking like a different person
そりゃあ今日も美しい
Well, of course you're beautiful today too
出会って思ったんだ you choose me
I thought when we met, you choose me
けれどあの頃の君はもう
But the you from back then is already...
マボロシの様にフッとなくなりそう
...about to suddenly vanish like a phantom
それがフラッシュしてバックすんだ
It flashes and backs up
目が回るんだ
My head is spinning
グルグル グルグル
Round and round, round and round
ホントはきっともう
In truth, surely by now...
戻れないよねえ
...we can't go back, right?
ちらつく心
My flickering heart
キミが探してよ ほら
Find me, look
Yo ほら!
Yo, look!
フラフラするでしょう
You're feeling unsteady, aren't you?
クラクラ来るでしょう
You're feeling dizzy, aren't you?
ホロホロとろけそう そうでしょう
Looks like you're about to melt away, right?
FLASH BANG
ギラギラ今宵の show
The dazzling show tonight
さあさあ踊りましょう
Come on, let's dance
真っ白く目眩むほど
So dazzlingly pitch white
ほら 焼き付けてよ FLASH BANG
Look, burn it in, FLASH BANG
FLASH BANG
Woohoo! Nice job Chad Cast!
Pach pach pach pach!
Clap clap clap clap!
Well done, you guys got some moves!
Oh god. What's she doing?
What's she doing?
IRyS, you good? I was thinking you could use a little rest.
I think you could... What is she doing?
It's... Hey, hey, it's okay.
IRyS, I think... I think you guys need to go relax.
You guys need to go...
Oh, okay. Okay. That's great.
Have some fun at the resort, you know there's a cool bar over there, and there's a yoga statue...
Resort! Resort! Resort, let's go!
Yay! Run!
Go, go, go, go!
Bye you two.
Oh god, I have a feeling it's about to get real wild back there. Maybe we should do another song though, in the meantime, huh?
Bye guys. They're gone.
They'll have fun. Don't worry about them.
Let's, um... let's do another song, shall we?
Let's go!
My camouflage
What you gonna do? Shit, take a walk!
Play the role of bad girl, like I had a choice
I could be your seiso, should you say so, hush my voice
Double take, go figure!
A disappearing act, no-no-no
Secret sinners, so you rang? Can't fool me like tick-tick bang
カモフラ there you go
Camouflage, there you go
マル秘な逃避行
A secret escape
どこまでも匿名希望
Anonymous, wherever we go
Excuse to see some proof it's me
Flip all that, don't react, eyes right here
Woah-oh, so crazy, what 'chu on?
Predicting all my flaws
But all you're seeing is my camouflage
Woah-overload!
Hey dead beat, why so shocked?
Your Mona Lisa talks
Still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
My camouflage, my camouflage
My camouflage, what you gonna do? Shit, take a walk!
Come alive, cuz' I shift with the scene and vibe
And I'm shuffling with the movement
Steal a glance, stop, no chance. This who you gotta be
カモフラ where you go
Camouflage, where you go
壁側の向こう
Over on the wall's side
すり抜ける この包囲網
Slipping through this dragnet
Excuse to see some proof it's me
Flip all that, don't react, eyes right here
Woah-oh, so crazy, what 'chu on?
Predicting all my flaws
But all you're seeing is my camouflage
Woah-overload!
Hey dead beat, why so shocked?
Your Mona Lisa talks
Still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
my camouflage
what'cha gonna do ? shit , take a walk !
What'cha gonna do? Shit, take a walk!
my camouflage
what'cha gonna do ? shit , take a walk !
What'cha gonna do? Shit, take a walk!
hey why so shocked
shit ( s ) take a walk
Shit, take a walk!
my camouflage
still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
can't fight no more …
Can't fight no more...
hide away . hide away .
Hide away, hide away...
what is this dark side hiding for ?
What is this dark side hiding for?
ain't it something ?
Ain't it something?
ain't i something ? ain't it something ?
Ain't I something? Ain't it something?
whoah - oh !
Whoah-oh!
so crazy , what ' chu on ? predicting all my flaws
So crazy, what'chu on? Predicting all my flaws...
but all you ' re seeing is my camouflage
...but all you're seeing is my camouflage.
whoah - overload ! hey dead beat , why so shocked ?
Whoah, overload! Hey, deadbeat, why so shocked?
your mona lisa talks
still ain't nothing new , shit , can't y ' all knock ?
Still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
whoah - oh !
Whoah-oh!
so crazy , what ' chu on ? predicting all my flaws
So crazy, what'chu on? Predicting all my flaws...
but all you ' re seeing is my camouflage
...but all you're seeing is my camouflage.
whoah - overload ! hey dead beat , why so shocked ?
Whoah, overload! Hey, deadbeat, why so shocked?
your mona lisa talks
still ain't nothing new , shit , can't y ' all knock ?
Still ain't nothing new, shit, can't y'all knock?
my camouflage
what'cha gonna do ? shit , take a walk !
What'cha gonna do? Shit, take a walk!
my camouflage
what'cha gonna do ? shit , can't y ' all knock ?
What'cha gonna do? Shit, can't y'all knock?
guess i gotta use this camouflage
バウバウ！バウバウ！
Bau bau! Bau bau!
バウバウ、バウ、バウ、バウ、バウ、バウ！
Bau bau, bau, bau, bau, bau, bau!
Hi! Oh...
...thank you guys for dancing with me today!
And you guys sound so good too!
Cute! You're really taller. Oh my gosh!
Oh, I'm being hugged! I'm being hugged!
Oh, wait, go enjoy the resort, you guys.
Have fun!
Go get some rest. Bye-bye. There are doggy treats over there, maybe.
Go find them. Go find them.
They're gonna go look for the treats.
Ah, maybe... maybe I should relax here for a little bit.
No! We have more songs to do, Deadbeats.
No rest for the wicked. So, while my friends are enjoying the resort...
...I'm gonna go do some more work. Just for a little bit, though.
We can come back later, right? Yeah, that's what I'm gonna do.
Let's get out of here.
No, no, we can come back later. We can come back later.
I'm out. I'm outski, I'm out.
Yeah, don't, don't worry, don't worry about, about those guys.
Hey, listen, in fairness, don't worry about the Xbox mic either.
I did that to them on purpose.
It was not them, it was me. I cursed their mics with Xbox mic syndrome...
...because... I'm choking on my own spit.
Because, because...
...their voices are too cute and...
...they needed to be nerfed. That's all it was, but...
...no, it's not, it's not their fault.
You sure? It was all me.
How dare you! That's fine.
I will take, I will take your insults.
I will take all of them.
Also, if my friends, if my friends ever need me to come in for a song...
...and, like, tank all the bad words, let me know.
I'll do it. I went through...
I went through a period in the past five years, I was like...
Yeah, we can walk and talk, we can walk and talk.
I went through a period of time within the past five years being like...
"You know what? Maybe I should calm down with the curse words."
But, but it's just because, you know, I'm getting to be an old woman, right?
As you can see, I'm walking like a decrepit, a crotchety old lady...
...with my shoulders all the way down.
But honestly, if it's for a song, who cares, right?
It's just, just for F-word.
Yeah, speed walking. Good old curse words.
We stay family-friendly but to be honest...
To be honest, I've...
I've heard children use fouler language than I've ever used...
...in my life, so you know what? It is what it is.
It is what it is. Look like I'm rapidly roller skating?
Maybe that's what I'm doing. Maybe there are skates on the bottom of these shoes...
...and you guys don't even know.
Anyway, um, I look like less of a robber, don't you think?
Without the beanie.
I look a little bit less like I'm gonna break into your home...
...which is, you know, a plus or minus depending upon how you view it, but...
I can take my headphones off, too.
See, they're, they're gone.
They're gone. I don't really know...
I mean, it kind of covers my jewelry, so it's kind of nice that you can see...
...the finer details, right?
So, I've got like a little skull lapel. Jacket.
Lapel? Maybe it's just a pin.
I don't know, but I'm really into chokers these days, and spikes...
...and stuff like that, so, yeah.
Law-abiding Reaper. Oh, but of course, but of course.
Definitely. Looking respect... Oh, of course, yeah.
Looking... checking respect... Yeah, only with respect.
With respect.
What do you guys think?
Do you like the inside of my jacket, too?
It's got got like a checker pattern.
Anyway, we're, we're supposed to be moving...
...and right along, but I'm gonna take my time around here as well.
We do have many more memories to... to re-familiarize ourselves with though, so.
Let me... Let me grab you.
Oh, don't worry, you won't feel it, and it won't hurt.
Okay, I've grabbed you successfully.
Let me... Hold on. Swirl eyes, what do those look like?
Hang on, oh, I'm still on desktop. Okay.
Swirl-ized.
Uh...
She is a little quirky and crazy.
But it makes me like her more, I guess, I don't know.
If you're still here after five years, you got... certainly got some taste.
If you're still here after five years, you've certainly got some taste.
All right, let's go ahead and move!
I love the architecture in this place.
Lots of respect to the Underworldian culture here.
With our... our Underworldian Maidens.
I don't know who this lady is. Could this be the real Calliope?
Could it be? The real muse, Calliope... It could be.
If it isn't, then that's now my headcanon, but...
But, I probably should change my... my eyes to not be so swirly, sorry about that.
I'm just being extra quirky today.
Lore, whomst?
I'm telling you, I think that it's the original Calliope. We're gonna move with respect right behind her.
And I wanted to say I saw this before but I didn't want to get too ahead of myself.
Check this out, guys, where are we?
What is this place? You can see the sky and the fragments...
But then beyond, there's like a swirling deserted city.
And then I see that there's like... I'm really interested in the Hell Temple that's over here.
Do you guys see that Hell Temple? I think we should go there next.
It reminds me of something that I've seen before on multiple levels, right?
I think that you guys might be able to draw the links between the places that we're visiting today...
...and also some VR shenanigans that we've gotten down to in the past, right? But...
But for now, it looks cool. Yay!
Design is wild, right? Isn't it awesome?
We're going home. Onto the next stage indeed, Dead Beats, indeed.
Like from J-RAP in Jigoku?
J-RAP in Jigoku was... was my concert, right?
But Jigoku 6 is my EP.
Maybe it's not the best idea to use the same... the same word in my concert/shows because people might get confused.
Anyway, we're going over the bridge to check out what the heck this place is.
I love lanterns, so the aesthetic is pretty much on point...
...for what I enjoy, but...
Hold on, I'm getting that... weird feeling again...
...like I've been here before.
Hang on a sec. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hold up.
You see that? It's one of those... one of those camera signs.
What if we touch it? Hold on a sec.
Let me see that camera... camera right here.
This should give a sweeping view. Okay, check it out.
Whoa!
Okay, now I'm feeling ultra-nostalgic.
Huh, I feel like this isn't the first time that I've entered this place, though.
Like I've... I've seen it before.
I think I feel a memory coming on, you guys, a memory singing a song with someone here.
Well, if that's the case then... let's... let's check it out!
Oh, this place is pretty cool, too. Hey, there's cool stuff everywhere.
Especially... this is awesome, it's got lanterns!
What the heck, didn't I dance in front of that fire during Jigoku 6?
Hey, is that the pirate from the Future Island...
...stage that was in the Jigoku 6 concert?
It has to be. This place is awesome. This is so cool, what the heck.
I wonder, are there any friends around here, too? What friends are here, I wonder.
Huh? Oh, oh, oh.
Are you okay? Oh, she's climbing up those stairs.
I know there's a lot of stairs. Jimooine, are you okay?
I know it was a lot of stairs. She's really wheezing.
Oh god. Are you okay, little one?
I'm alive.
This place is flames.
Hey there.
Hi!
You're so cute.
I can see a lot of things from down here.
I know you can. I figured as much.
Whoa, hey, don't look too long, though. Whoa there, she's a little close.
You got such a big head here. I didn't expect to see you like this.
Oh my lord, ugh!
What, you don't want me?
No, no, I have no problem with...
There, really, what is it... the Hougei? It really stinks.
Oh my god! Ouch! Ouch!
Why are you beating on me? Hey!
Oi, oi, omai... omai...
Hey, hey, you... you...
Come over! Quick! Quick!
Stop, stop it! Go get her!
Why are you so crazy?
That's okay, I know the answer. I know the answer.
What's the answer?
I love you so much though.
I love you more, Calliope. I can't wait to...
Oh god.
...do so many things with you.
I want to do some things with you too, but one of those things is... sing. One, sing.
Sing on this stage in front of this fire.
Name two.
Um... dance on this stage in front of this fire.
Okay, what's the third one though?
Um... be beside you.
Does it start with kissing me?
Uh, maybe later. We can... not...
...not in front of the people.
Uh, depends on where, too. You may kiss my hand if you want.
Eww! I would never!
Okay, yeah, that's...
Perfect, perfect. All right, that's great.
Shall we... shall we sing a little... a little song?
Oh god, I'm flustered now.
All right, let's... let's sing a dang song together. How about it?
All right, play music!
Check 1, 2. Hey! Ready!
Hey! Hey! Mori-chi! JiJi-muri!
Let's go! Are you listening?
Lined up, one by one, to play the toy soldiers of a corporation
Shorn down to the 1 on 1 あたしらの一等賞 ターゲット
Shorn down to the 1-on-1, we are the grand prize target
さあ、やってやりましょう
Now, let's get to it
Are you entertained now? Let the karma rain down
I can play the Pierrot if it means I'll be the last clown
Living in the twisted diorama that is industry
Failing when we're in the streets, making all those...
今夜の変身 決め手は様々
Tonight's transformation, there are various deciding factors
一生の私に 夢見ておいでよ
Come dream of being together with me for a lifetime
おいでよ ほら平気？ worldplay, holler
Come on, see, are you okay? Worldplay, holler
君とだからさ Let's dig in!
Because it's with you, let's dig in!
Mirror, mirror, show me, tell me again
Is there one prettier than the media's own stroke?
Don't look
Louder, clearer, just say that I'm enough
You lie so well, mirror, mirror
一触即発で取り込もう
Let's capture it on the verge of explosion
Yeah, yeah, are you ready? Go!
Hate to be the one to break the fairy tale apart, but
I can pack the cash up, miserly, what, are they smart?
Touted, nobody cries, step now and fall behind
Every idol beauty's got a beast inside her mind
Write to mock the whole fold-out magazine of things you said but didn't mean
It's real like a run of lighter fluid, stains will never clean
Or wash away...
空気ですね、生かせる、そんなもんじゃない人生
It's like air, make use of it, life is not just that
勝者とゲーム、焦がれるなギブ
Winner and game, don't yearn to give
混ざる、もう、小さくチェンジな勝負
Mix, already, a small-change game
僕、僕ではない、無くなった、骨格、核
Me, not me, gone, skeleton, core
矢印はいつもアンタ、全然から、高架下
The arrow is always you, completely, from under the elevated tracks
旅にもっと、商員、頼むのは一度きり
More reasons to travel, asking only once
解き明かせ、場所の、神メニュー
Solve it, the location's god menu
取れない、中、勝ち、分かっちゃう、価値
Can't take, inside, win, realize the value
乗れない、だらけの、恐怖、巧みな、身
Can't ride, full of fear, skillful body
渡そう
Let's hand it over
SOS, SOS, 私は誰？ 光が遠すぎる
SOS, SOS, who am I? The light is too far away
Oh, mirror, mirror, mirror, 死に神だって、髪、乱れて
Oh, mirror, mirror, mirror, even the Grim Reaper has disheveled hair
よくぞ通った、なりそう、今日
Well done passing through, it seems likely today
ならばデスティニー on my way, GO!
If so, destiny on my way, GO!
一触即発で飛び込もう
Let's dive in with touch-and-go volatility
Mirror, mirror, 本当の私はどこ？
Mirror, mirror, where is the real me?
ジョークだらけの、お疲れ様
Full of jokes, thank you for your hard work
うちらはだらだらしごとし、デパート
We work lazily, department
取り残され、ワールドプレイハラ
Left behind, worldplay, holler
世の、狂わす自然、通りを、勝っていくフラワー
Winning the street, flower that drives the world mad
Yeah, breaking down, なんでも、あたし、がいれば、アカン, Hey, Hey, Hey
Yeah, breaking down, anything, if I'm here, no good, Hey, Hey, Hey
群れて、退治した、ちょっとの、魂
Flocked together, exterminated, a little soul
世界を殺すな、合格
Don't kill the world, pass
Diggy, diggy, diggy, good job, mic check
戯言から進行、女王、アイドール
Progressing from nonsense, queen, idol
愛取る、愛、召し、美道中 Keep it up!
Taking love, love, meal, beautiful journey, Keep it up!
ヘラヘラ、仕事、しに、そんな、見込み 魅力、お仕事
Giggling to work, such expectation, charm, work
Excellent!
Capitulate to follow the irrelevant
You only got a cell of it, you only got to get out of your celibate
And if you ever make it, better hope that you can take it with you
Still as good as naked, it's a living or a trust to break
I don't care anymore!
I'm freaking out!
What's she doing?
I'm freaking out! I'm freaking out! Yeah, yeah!
It's just business
Mirror, mirror, show me, tell me again
Is there one prettier than the media's own stroke?
Don't look
Louder, clearer, just say that I'm enough
You lie so well, mirror, mirror
一触即発で飛び込もう
Let's dive in with touch-and-go volatility
Parasite, parasite, hell of a parasite
I'm up on the stage and I hate him, I'll be loving, living, life control
Let the record spin on like a carousel
Oh my god, it's a mad, mad world!
It's a paradise, いつか見たい、尊いもの
It's a paradise, I want to see a precious thing someday
そんなもの、最期でしょう
That kind of thing must be the end
儚い、空、待つ、絶望、望むなら、大往生
Fleeting sky, waiting despair, if you wish, dying in peace
歌おう
Let's sing!
I remember Gigi was freaking it to you guys!
She was freaking it!
I think it's super cute...
...that I feel, I get the feeling that only she has chosen to be in that form.
Only Gigi wanted to be so, so small and rotund and cute.
Anyway, I guess we should look around a little.
She does that all the time. I see some Grems in here know what's up.
Gigi... Gigi is special.
Oh, I love... I love her very much.
She's always so nice and fun to hang out with.
I was so glad that I could, I could sing on a stage like this with her.
Speaking of the stage, should we look around a little bit?
Here, follow me! What's this?
This seems like a really cool view over here.
I love that the lanterns have like this Myth, Myth logo on them. Check it!
You guys see? Look! And they glow in like red, and yellow, and...
And you can see so many different areas just from here.
Myth forever, right guys?
See that place over there? That...
Is that, is that Atlantis?
I want to go to Atlantis! Wait, we can't get ahead of ourselves though.
There are a lot of different places to look at but...
Oh man, I guess we can, we can look at a little bit more of this area.
Let's see.
As I mentioned before in the memory, that, that pirate, is that the pirate from the...
from the Future Island performance from Jigoku 6, the concert?
I think it is! Look at that big guy.
And it says, I think that's the kanji for 'King' on his... Oh gosh, there's fire in my eyes.
We don't want to fall down there, but if we did fall down there, something cool might happen.
Maybe there's a secret underneath that fire.
I want to discover the secrets, but there will be time to look at secrets later, I think.
I'm getting really... getting really hot, Dead Beats.
Doesn't feel so good.
But the heat is reminding me of something.
The heat is reminding me that...
I think that... this wasn't the only performance that I did here.
I think there was another one...
...with two, with two other people.
If I stand here, I might be able to...
...remember.
All right. I think I do.
Okay. Check it out!
Players down in hell all want it the same
Flawless and cautious, oh what a hecking shame
清楚なdeathちゃん knows your sick game
The prim and proper Miss Death knows your sick game
Shake it
I'm a walking disaster
Not half-cocked like the last girl
Ya say stop, I go faster
Talkin' slaughter and laughter, boom-boom-bang
Act a fool, I'm a misfit
A "too cool" nihilist chick
Think I wanna blow up this niche
Arrogant and loud, I might hit her like a light switch, pow
I'm such a cosmic pain
魅惑の痛み shut up, I ain't no hero
An alluring pain, shut up, I ain't no hero
サバイバルできんの？
Can you even survive?
Hey
Got devils in my brain, can't make 'em shut up
Next, you'll say you're fed up
Nah, this is what I led ya to
Forget "sport", this is war
What ya waiting for?
Good Lord, Mori's bored
Welcome to the killing floor!
Got no will to run, don't look at me like I'm dumb
Doomers swear "life ain't fair", I don't care!
The end is nigh
End is nigh
Didn't get the memo yet? End is nigh
Boys, line up single file
Wanna end the world in style
Get on some Armageddon stuff like
Gotta kill 'em all から end is nigh
Gotta kill 'em all, so the end is nigh
Players down in hell all want it the same
Flawless and cautious, oh what a...
Get a grip, red does not mean go
死, not your 虜
Death, not your captive
死 on the new world order's throne
Death on the new world order's throne
Does that make you see?
Brace for the apocalypse, they hate my guts so read my lips
Don't take the bait, stick to the script
Play 'em like a fool when they numbers dip
Say what now? Make 'em shut down
Yeah, Shinigami gang in a rough town
Break new ground, black and blue sound
まだまだぶちかましたい next round!
We're still gonna blow it out next round!
Aah, what's on your mind? Don't want to die?
Price is a little bit of ego
Cynics wanna sit in these robes
Empress got hella new clothes!
Forget "sport", this is war
What ya waiting for?
Good Lord, Mori's bored
Welcome to the killing floor!
Life ain't ever fair, but hold up then, what's this?
Naturally that means death is justice!
Lemme liberate you, 世界が hates you
Lemme liberate you, the world hates you
We can make 'em pay, too! Ban-bab-ba-ban!
The end is nigh
End is nigh
Didn't get the memo yet? End is nigh
...drown in fire
Lost inside in this dark desire
No love, no faith, just you and I
Dancing 'til the end of time
Gotta end this night
Hahaha!
Ra-ta-ta-ta-ta!
Don't want it to end!
End this night!
Yeah! Let's end this night
Yeah, something's gotta give
Gonna burn that ratchet, live
Gotta get 'em all, gotta end this night
Let's end this night
Woo! Yeah, yeah!
All right!
Big up, our endless!
Come on!
Ra-ta-ta-ta, end this night
We Are Currently Experiencing Technical Difficulties. Please Hold!
Oh, where am I?
Hang on.
Hang on, guys.
Where... where are my Dead Beats?
Where... I think I found them.
Hang on.
Ugh...
My Dead Beats...
Oh gosh, I feel like I have to go pick up my special camera.
My special camera, I left it... I left it at the... the other... the other place.
Yeah, that performance was a little too hot, you guys.
Uh, I think it destroyed... it destroyed the computer, it destroyed...
VRChat, it destroyed everything.
That's how hot of a performance that was.
Hold on, let's... I bet we can cut through here really quick to get my camera.
Ugh... ugh...
Hang on. Well...
You guys know how it's been the past five years.
There's always a little surprise guest...
...some scuff.
I... I like to believe that EN has moved on from all of that, but occasionally, it will creep back up on me.
That's okay. No problem.
I'm going to grab my camera.
Okay.
Where'd it go?
Whew! Quite the workout.
But I got it. Hello.
As you can see, I'm, um...
What if we just...
I think I got the power to teleport. Oh! Okay.
Okay.
I'm going to get the camera.
What did you guys think of the Hell Temple?
I figured maybe we could move right along though.
Um, there are some secrets around the Hell Temple...
...that I think we'll leave for a little bit later. But for now...
...I wanted to say, do you guys see that hand over here?
What is this?
This is some end of the world stuff.
Look at that.
Do you see that hand?
It's just, what's the hand doing there?
What if I were to stand on the hand and do some poses?
Maybe we can get some poses of me standing on the hand?
This is like some...
...some Evangelion stuff, you know?
It's just me and my skeleton at the end of the world, standing on a hand.
What's the hand doing? What's the hand doing?
Let me pull my Dead Beats closer to me. Hang on a sec.
Okay, pull. I'm pulling you closer.
I'm reeling you in like you're a fish on a hook.
Giant skelly.
Yeah, let's grab some screenshots if you want.
This is Mori Calliope posing on a hand.
Wait, I should do something super whimsical.
What if I did a pose with like no eyeballs or something? Hang on.
'Cause that could be fun. No eyes.
What she doing? What she doing?
What she doing on the hand?
What she doing on the...
Did you know I could stretch my leg this far? Oh god, I'm going to fall!
No, it's no problem. I'm just being super... being super whimsical.
Do a backflip? I can't. I can't.
Tracking's just too, too good over here. It's too good.
It's not possible.
I'm, I'm too busy doing real body tracking.
Anyway, you guys want to... I want to get my eyes back.
Ugh, it's been a crazy day, huh?
Well, let's, let's go ahead and check out the city...
...because there's some stuff here that I wanted to look at, so...
And not just the hand, but...
Check this out. What is this little arena over here?
With all this debris...
Actually, the word is debris.
Oh, maybe we can get a better look.
Hang on, would you guys like a better look at this place?
Because I would like a better look at this place. What if we...
Oh, hey guys! I found one of those camera thingies.
Uh, if I press this button, we might be able to get...
Ooh! Check it!
It's a delap... dilapidated...
...dilapidated city.
Is that... Is that Big Papa Dead Beat?
Could that be the Papa Reaper up there?
Was that event held here? You would think, right?
See, that's the kind of vibe that I'm getting...
...from this place, this dilapidated city.
And that's a Dead Beat being chained by his neck.
Maybe we could save him? I feel bad.
That's actually my house? Oh god, I'm sorry, Dead Beat.
I didn't mean to show your house like that in front of everybody.
Aw, I'm sorry. Wait, that was an accident.
Aw. But look, this...
People really could live here.
Would I choose to live... Maybe I should build my house here.
Because I'm looking into building a house, right, Dead Beats?
I mentioned that. Maybe I should build my house here.
Oh, you guys want to see something cool, actually?
There's, there's something that I haven't shown you I can do with this outfit.
You're really close. I'm really close to you.
Hi!
Um...
Check this out. Hold on.
I'm, I'm changing. Don't look.
Okay, here we go.
No jacket.
No jacket Mori Calliope!
Check it out!
My hand's doing funny things. Did you know that I have...
...I have 50 extra tendons in my hands.
A peace sign, let me do a peace.
Peace!
Handycam!
Shoulders exposed!
No way.
That looks pretty cool, though. Perfect for summertime, right?
Although, I get the feeling if I put on the beanie, I would definitely look...
...like a robber.
In that case.
What can you do?
Nothing much, but summer just ended. Did it, really?
I don't feel like it's ended. I feel like we still got a ways to go, but...
Yeah, back to the relevant subject here.
Back to the relevant subject. We're in this dilapidated city.
Isn't this cool?
I'd love to just rest my legs, but I feel like...
...another memory is coming on, you know?
Another like, I've been here before and sang some songs with some friends.
So...
Would you guys like to see that?
Maybe we can both have a brain blast together.
Channel your, your third eye.
Channel the inner part of your brain to remember things that you forgot.
That's something that I could really, honestly...
...do, more often.
It'll be very helpful for me.
But anyway,
let's go ahead and run the memory!
Cult Following
[Title: Cult Following]
Cut your other ties
This ain't the only battlefield I can televise
Ego is an armor
so put the camera down and face it
They went and got complacent
Come and run with me
You say you stand for nothing, no one else can relate
Just know the company you keep is in the business of hate
Are you afraid?
Don't run away, I'm close to getting paid
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
Go and shoot, shoot, shoot
Aw, baby, did you miss?
Ricochet, ricochet
You can think about me anytime of any day
Forget your street fights
This a trench war
I'll make you march, march, march 'til you hit the floor
Getting thirsty for collision
Let them wonder what they're missing
in the front row, lock and load
Now here we go
This ain't a lifeline
It's a call to arms
Become the risen, the unforgiven, make a decision
If you're looking for permission to riot, you got it wrong
Say goodbye to your identity, click, flash, now you belong
The situation isn't fluid at all
Took out my reddest paints and markers, and I ruined the wall
It's not that complicated
I could choose to run, but I crawl
To slit the ankles of the skeptics who are wishing we fall
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
Go and shoot, shoot, shoot
Aw, baby, did you miss?
Ricochet, ricochet
You can think about me anytime of any day
Forget your street fights
This a trench war
I'll make you march, march, march 'til you hit the floor
Getting thirsty for collision
Let them wonder what they're missing
in the front row, lock and load
Now here we go
This ain't a lifeline
It's a call to arms
Become the risen, the unforgiven, make a decision
If you're looking for permission to riot, you got it wrong
Say goodbye to your identity, click, flash, now you belong
I'll be dancing on my own in a bulletproof vest
They can shoot, shoot, shoot, and we'll see who shoots best
Fighting all our battles, know the kind too well
They go "Ready, set, rage," then they follow us to hell
Finger on the trigger, 'bout to cock it and run
Got a lyric in the chamber, but I'm aiming my own gun
Forget your street fights
This a trench war
I'll make you march, march, march 'til you hit the floor
Getting thirsty for collision
Let them wonder what they're missing
in the front row, lock and load
Now here we go
This ain't a lifeline
It's a call to arms
Become the risen, the unforgiven, make a decision
If you're looking for permission to riot, you got it wrong
Say goodbye to your identity, click, flash, now you belong
Let them riot onward, lock and load
Stand for nothing, play the coward
Stand by someone, you're devoured
It's a sick and twisted miscreant's existence
Let them riot onward, lock and load
Stand for nothing, play the coward
Stand by someone, you're devoured
It's a sick and twisted miscreant's existence
Errors creeping through the core
Protocols failing
System collapse in three, two, one
OVER//RIDE
[Title: OVER//RIDE]
ノイズの中のノイズ 脳内リピート
The noise inside the noise repeating in my brain...
Trust, faith, 想像通り delete
Trust, faith, deleted just as imagined.
モラルも正義も単なるコード
Morality and justice are merely code.
シャットダウンしてI rewrite what is mine
Shut it down, and I rewrite what is mine.
生身を蝕むパラサイト
A parasite eating away at my living flesh...
貫き通して、射止めるだけ
Only to penetrate and hit the target.
迷路？ 行き止まり？ バグ？ 狂うマインド？
A maze? A dead end? A bug? A crazed mind?
リライト×リライト×リライト×リライト
Rewrite, rewrite, rewrite, rewrite!
何度も奪われても
Even if it's taken away many times,
何度も壊されても
even if it's destroyed many times...
それでもまだ
Even so, still...
戦う
I will fight.
抗い、進め、本能を宿して
Resist, move forward, harboring our instincts!
Override, override ゼロの光を放つ
Override, override, emitting zero's light!
この壊れた世界で、証明を叫ぶ
In this broken world, we scream our proof!
No rewind, no reset 覚悟のその先に咲く花がある
No rewind, no reset, there's a flower blooming beyond our resolve!
...が流る
...flowing
ループじゃない 選んだ道だ
It's not a loop! It's the path I chose!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Over, over, override!
We fall, we rise, we override!
Lalala...
Splitting atoms in the air, can't expect them all to care
Lost inside nightmares, shed the fear, strip it bare
Leash emotions, make a stance
In the end, it's going nowhere, drowned in loops
What's the truth? Rise up, gonna break the chains!
描いていくイメージ 抗うファイアウォール
An image drawn, resisting the firewall
Just once more stand, togu steel your soul
Just once more stand, steel your soul
Cry out, let's go, broken dream
Rewind, rewind, rewind, rewind
戻らない
No turning back
たとえ何度も閉ざされても
Even if we are shut out again and again
この手でまた
With these hands once more...
繋げ 描け 創れ 終焉の扉 開け
Connect, draw, create, open the door to the end
Override! Override! 嵐の中の光を掴め
Override! Override! Seize the light within the storm
掴め
Seize it
この命尽きるまで 真実をかざして
Until this life ends, hold up the truth
No rewind, no reset, 選んだこの道に咲く花がある
No rewind, no reset, there's a flower that blooms on the path I chose
ループじゃない 生まれ落ちた意味を
It's not a loop! The meaning of being born...
Fight! Fight! Fight! Over, over, override! We fall, we rise, we override!
崩れだした世界で
In this crumbling world...
声だけが響いて
Only our voices echo
烈火のごとく焼き尽くせ
Burn it all down like a raging fire
限界を蹴り飛ばせ
Kick away the limits!
宿命をねじ伏せろ
Overpower fate!
Zero out of despair, now!
Override! Override! 天の向こうへ響く声上げろ
Override! Override! Raise your voice echoing to the other side of heaven!
この痛みを超えて 最果てへ向かえ
Cross beyond this pain, head towards the very end
No rewind, no reset, カオスの先へ 咲く花がある
No rewind, no reset, there's a flower that blooms beyond the chaos
ループじゃない 選んだ道だ
It's not a loop! It's the path I chose!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Over, over, override! We fall, we rise, we override!
Lalala...
She died!
Do you guys remember when Nerissa Ravencroft died?
'Cause I do!
Uh, these have been really fun, these memories.
I've really enjoyed looking through them with you guys.
I saw somebody in chat said 'Help, is she on desktop?' No, she's in the world with us!
But you know, a desktop is very helpful for folks who cannot...
...who cannot be present in the exact place or do not have full body capabilities at the moment.
But you know, I think despite all the technical...
...technical walls that we've had, you know...
...bringing this nostalgic trip down memory lane to light...
...everything... everything has been so interesting and fun the whole time, and...
...and I'm just so happy to be able to spend that with you guys...
...to show you guys this amazing creation.
Look at that Dead Beat! Look at...
...me and the Dead Beat. Don't be shy, come back!
There's the Dead Beat.
There's the Dead Beat!
That's a Dead Beat. That's a Dead Beat for you.
Mori Calli peak. I like that. Can we start using...?
You can if you want, I won't- I won't say it but, if- if you want to.
It makes me happy, it makes me happy that you enjoy... What if I jump?
I'm jumping.
Seeing if that makes a difference in anything, like if the camera can really handle the... the full...
...capacity of my jumps.
Anyway, we're kind of... we don't have all the time in the world, but you know we... if we want to look at...
...secrets.
If we want to look at the secrets, we probably got to get moving a little bit, but there's one...
...there's one special secret that I want to look at before we move on to... the Faded Atlantis...
...that I'm really excited about checking out. Do you guys want to go?
If you don't know where it is, you may have noticed, if you look yonder...
...if you look way over there...
...you can see that there's a black square in the... in the cliffside.
Way over there.
In the cliffside of the plaza. So I was thinking maybe we could go there.
There's a little secret over here.
Perhaps it leads to... another memory?
I don't know, I'm kind of nervous. I feel like...
...what if this... well, what if, what if we're not able to get back? I mean...
the ominous square in the wall.
Typically, if you see a square... hidden wall.
Visions of hidden walls.
Maybe I should roll through.
Like Dark Souls.
Walk on water.
Anyway, anyway.
Shall we go inside?
Whoa!
Hey!
I know this place.
Do you guys know this place?
Do you guys remember?
Oh man, it's...
...been a really long time, huh?
I know it, some of you were around for this, but...
...remember when we had...
...one of our... aw.
And see the banner, "Happy HoloMyth...
...2 Year Anniversary".
Blast from the past, right? The memories.
Remember when we all...
...sang and danced in an interesting way...
...on this stage?
And I remember we had so many things to announce back then.
And we did it in 360, too.
So, like, people could use their phone...
...and like sit in the center...
...and like rotate it around...
...and they could look at their oshi the whole time.
I wonder how many Deadbeats...
...were looking mostly at Mori.
You don't have to though, because there are...
...so many wonderful people to enjoy and support, but...
...but if you did look at me lots, I'd...
...I'd be really happy.
I want to do something like that again...
...someday, actually.
Kind of walking around this old place...
...and thinking that to myself, you know, like...
It'd be really cool to do something like that again.
And we can't forget the backstage, right?
You guys were allowed backstage, which is...
...very special, don't you think? Hold on.
Whoa!
Remember we had you guys sit...
We had you guys sit right there...
...on this stool.
In this exact spot.
Back in the day.
It's all kind of dark and dimly lit now.
Since it was so long ago.
Somehow it still feels like home, you know?
I'd really love, I'd love for you guys...
...to be able to visit this spot, too.
But... maybe you'll be able to.
Well, we'll talk about that a little bit later, but...
...I guess we better get out of here.
We got... we got an Atlantis to look at.
So, let's get... let's get moving, I guess.
As much as I would love to sit here...
...and just reminisce about...
...everything that's happened, right?
I think... maybe we should go ahead...
...and get moving.
Before I get too sentimental.
All right.
Well...
Let's go!
"I'm happy you're with us, Calli."
I'm happy I'm here.
Thank you for making it fun to be here.
Well, it's a happy occasion, right?
We should be... we should be happy...
...and excited for the future!
So, let's... let's go!
We're going, we're going...
...but a moment of quiet reflection...
...is fun too, don't you think?
I think so.
Uh, the way to Atlantis is kind of far...
...so I hope you guys can keep up with me.
Get running, Deadbeats, we're running, we're running.
All this training I've been doing...
...and I still feel like I'm not...
...in enough shape to be doing this!
But we're going, we're going.
Atlantis time, Atlantis time!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Here we go!
Oh, here we are.
Got there. Okay.
This is another one of those...
Oh, neat.
Right?
Check this out. Whoa!
That's Atlantis.
Atlantis finally! At last we get to see it.
I feel like this is based off of...
...a room of a good friend of mine.
Do you guys remember Gura's Atlantis room?
It was based off of her.
Kind of makes me think of that.
Hey, but what the heck is Council...
Is that CouncilRys?
It might be CouncilRys, I'm not totally sure, but...
...uh, before we jump in there...
...I'm getting the feeling...
...that I've entered this place before.
Well, shall we go ahead and take a look at another...
...musical... couple of musical...
...memories before we get too deep...
...into exploring, shall we?
All right, Deadbeats.
Play...
...run... run the memor...
I'm having a brain melt. If you guys...
「ラスト、行くよ」
Last, here it goes.
「おお、マップが切り替わる」
Ooh, the map is starting to swap.
「へえ、ここってアトランティス？」
Huh, is this supposed to be Atlantis?
「え、懐かしい思い出がたくさん」
Eh, so many memories.
「アトランティス、覚えてるよ。初代のVRチャットのMythマップにあった場所、全部覚えてる。すごく懐かしいな」
I remember Atlantis. I remember all the places that we had in the original, the original VRC Myth map. This brings back a lot of memories.
「でも、何かが少し違うよね？」
There's something kind of different though, right?
「この場所、何かが少し違う気がする」
There's something kind of different about this place.
「ええと、たとえば…」
Uh, like...
「あそこにいる人たちって、誰、誰、誰？」
Who, who, who are those people over there?
「見覚えのある人たちばかり。私の周りには見慣れた顔が並んでいる。見覚えのある顔」
I think I know these people. Familiar faces all around me. Familiar faces.
「でも、ここで誰かと一緒に歌いたいな。一体誰と歌うんだろう？」
I want to sing a song with someone here though. Who will I sing with here, I wonder?
「森！私ここだよ！」
Mori! I'm up here!
「ちょっと待って、何？あれって、しおり？」
Wait a minute, what? Is that, is that Shiori?
「上を見て！」
Look up here!
「待って、岩が見える。あんな高いところに岩が」
Wait, I see a rock. There's a rock way up there.
「カリ！今行くよ！降りていくからね！」
Calli! I'm coming down! I'm coming down!
「うん、おいで」
Yeah, come on.
「階段がたくさんあるけど…あ、そっか、彼女は階段なんて気にしないね」
Yeah, no problem. There's a lot of stairs. There's a lot of... Oh okay, I guess she doesn't care about the stairs.
「キャー！」
Oh god!
「な、何これ…？」
What the...?
「まるでレッキング・ボールみたいに突っ込んできたね。ハロー、しおり！」
Dang, you freaking came in like a wrecking ball there. Hi, Shiori!
「ハロー、カリ！」
Hi, Calli!
「ちっちゃいね」「素敵な衣装！」
You're so small. / Nice outfit!
「ありがとう。私の真新しい新衣装。どう思う？新しいギアだよ」
Thank you. My brand new, my brand new digs. What do you think? My new gear.
「おっと、ええと…」
Whoa, uh...
「ちょっと、ちょっと！そんなに近づかないで、しおり。ちょっと待って」
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Whoa there, don't get too close there, Shiori. Hold on a second.
「ハロー、カリ！」
Hi, Calli!
「いやいや、今日そんなことするの君が初めてじゃないと思うよ、たしか」
No, no, no, no. You're like... not the first person to do this today, I think.
「（笑い）」「やれやれ」
Hehehe... / Oh god.
「よく見せて。すごく素敵だよ」
Let me look at you. Look at you. You look so nice.
「ありがとう、嬉しいな。あなたも…私たち同じバンドのメンバーみたいだね」
Thank you. I appreciate... You look... We look like we're in the same band or something like that.
「アハ！」「何これ？見て、ヴォーギングしてる。私もできるよ」
Aha! / What the heck? Look at her, she's voguing. Oh my god, I can vogue too.
「私、彼女ほど上手じゃないや」
I'm not as good as she is.
「でもね、一緒に歌を歌うべきだと思うんだ。歌いたいでしょ？」
But, you know what? I think we should sing a song together. Do you want to sing a song?
「うん、一緒に歌おう！」
Yeah, let's sing a song together.
「すごく激しい（in-tense）曲を歌おう。ハードロックみたいな曲はどう？」
We should sing, we should sing something really intense. We should sing like a hard rock song, if you want.
「キャンプ（in tents）みたいに？」
Like camping?
「あ、違う。キャンプじゃないよ」
Uh, no. No camping, no camping.
「わかる？ テントの中（in tents）だから、キャンプでしょ？」
You get it? In tents... Like camping?
「ちょっと！しおり、やめてよ。ダジャレばかりで一伊那尓栖を思い出すじゃない。もう！」
Oh god. Shiori! Shiori, stop, you're going to... You're reminding me of Ina right now with the puns. Oh my god.
「叩いてやりたいけど、叩かないよ」「真面目に、真面目にするから」
I should smack you, but I won't. / I'll be, I'll be serious.
「真面目な曲を歌おう」
Let's sing something serious.
「うん、少しだけね。真面目すぎなくてもいいけど、それなりにね」
Yeah, just a little. It doesn't have to be too serious, you know, just serious enough, right?
「よし」
All right.
「じゃあ、始めよう。ミュージック、スタート！」
Let's run it then. Play music!
「スタート！」
Start!
テメェの所為です
It's your fault!
Overkill!
どのコが好き？
Which one do you like?
このコに決めた
I've chosen this one.
角度を調節
Adjusting the angle,
覚悟 微調節
fine-tuning my resolve.
飽きたらポイから
Throwing it away once bored,
place any bets
decide who is special and discard the rest
gambler by nature
chips start to stack
racing lovely animals until they crack
やいのやいの
Clamor and chatter,
貼り付け parasite
clinging parasite.
ヤンデレッテル
Yandere label,
テメェの所為です
it's your fault!
black out , break down
Black out, break down,
toss it when you've had enough
やっちゃえ イっちゃえ
Do it, lose yourself!
I can tell you 're not impressed
I can tell you're not impressed.
Hey, hey, hey...
右向け右
Turn to the right,
左向け左
turn to the left.
leave the defective , unworthy of investment
Leave the defective, unworthy of investment.
飽きたらポイから
Throwing it away once bored,
hot mess , worthless doll
hot mess, worthless doll.
よって たかって いらっしゃい
Come gather around, welcome.
gambler by nature
chips start to stack
racing lovely animals until they crack
beautiful dreams await modest hearts
close your eyes and all you'll see is black
talent
サイコパスと紙一重
thin line between that and a psychopath.
やってしまったの後悔で fever
With the fever of regretting what I've done,
もういい！
enough!
starving !
Starving!
時間のムダムダ
A waste, waste of time!
やっちゃえ イっちゃえ
Do it, lose yourself!
i can tell you 're not impressed
I can tell you're not impressed.
ウゼェ バカ アホ カス
Annoying, idiot, fool, trash,
こちら最下層
down here at the very bottom.
どうにかなりそう
Feels like I'm losing my mind,
どうにでもなりそう
feels like anything could happen.
ぶっとい絆
A thick bond...
lonely lonely
trouble in paradise
oh , if only
Oh, if only...
愛を唱えて
Chanting love,
「あいうえお」から「ん」まで昇って
climbing from 'A' to 'N',
見下してるわ
looking down upon you.
A-woah, a-a-woah, a-woah
才能
Talent,
サイコパスと紙一重
thin line between that and a psychopath.
やってしまったの後悔で fever
With the fever of regretting what I've done,
もういい！
enough!
starving !
Starving!
時間のムダムダ
A waste, waste of time!
やっちゃえ イっちゃえ
Do it, lose yourself!
i 'm the one that 's not impressed
I'm the one that's not impressed.
テメェの所為です
It's your fault!
愛されたいのに 会えない夢を見ているのは何故？
Why is it that I dream of us being unable to meet,
even though I want to be loved?
変えたい現実
The reality I want to change...
胸糞悪くて high になる
...is so sickening, it makes me high.
Wow...
Yeah, guess I took a leap,
no turning back point to go
looking deep inside for the cheat to exploit,
you know
あいるが こいつも そいつも どいつも driving me crazy
That guy, this guy, that guy,
everyone's driving me crazy.
wanted, wasted, sorry look in' faced kid,
can't stop falling down
tell me how I'm worthless, show ya where the dirt is,
one man's trash is another man's purpose
day one, flying high
come tomorrow, let me die
talk trash, choke and whine
nothing I own is truly mine
ごっくん
Gulp...
愛されたいのに 会えない夢を見ているのは何故？
Why is it that I dream of us being unable to meet,
even though I want to be loved?
変えたい現実 胸糞悪くて
The reality I want to change is so sickening...
high になる
...it makes me high.
やってって やってって やってって
Do it, do it, do it...
そのまま傷つけちゃって
...and just go ahead and hurt them.
期待裏切る bad ending
An expectation-betraying bad ending.
円から抜け出せない エンドロール
A credit roll unable to escape the loop.
演者は揃いも揃って クズに仕上げてちょうだい
The performers are all alike,
please make them into total trash.
整合性 正当性 正義の名の下
Consistency, legitimacy, under the name of justice...
下してやるわ game maker, undertaker
...I will hand down judgment,
game maker, undertaker.
脳天直下 くらえー
Straight down onto your crown, take this!
アンアン アンアン 響け
Ah-ah, ah-ah, echo!
mayday mayday
タンタン タンタン 鳴らす
Ding-dong, ding-dong, chiming.
聞こえないふりして逃げられると思ってんの？
Do you think you can escape
by pretending not to hear?
くっそ
Bullshit.
愛されたいのに 会えない夢を見ているのは何故？
Why is it that I dream of us being unable to meet,
even though I want to be loved?
変えたい現実 胸糞悪くて high になる
The reality I want to change is so sickening,
it makes me high.
不埒な声で 喘ぐ声は
With an outrageous voice, the gasping breath...
天国に近そうな気がしてた
...felt like it was close to heaven.
alright, all night, anger
狂おしく
...madly...
舞い上がっちまえ
...soar high up!
omg! omg! お前が お前が
OMG! OMG! You, you...
omg! omg! お前が
OMG! OMG! You...
omg! omg! omg! omg!
omg! omg!
傷つけちゃって
...ended up hurting...
Wow...
あーもう うざったい どうにかしておくんなまし
Ah, enough, how annoying.
Do something about it.
愛されたいのに 会えない夢を見ているのは何故？
Why is it that I dream of us being unable to meet,
even though I want to be loved?
変えたい現実 胸糞悪くて high になる
The reality I want to change is so sickening,
it makes me high.
不埒な声で 喘ぐ声は
With an outrageous voice, the gasping breath...
天国に近そうな気がしてた
...felt like it was close to heaven.
alright, all night, anger
狂おしく
...madly...
舞い上がっちまえ
...soar high up!
Wow...
足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough...
Wow... 足らない 足らない 足らない
Wow... Not enough, not enough, not enough...
Wow... 足らない 足らない 足らない 足らない
Wow... Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough!
Yeah yeah, Dead Beats, I know you saw that.
You saw staff-san flying around with the mute button.
Can you guess which, which memory song we, we sung first?
But in all seriousness, in all seriousness,
I want to give a huge shout out to all the staff that worked really, really hard on all of this because...
Honestly, this, this entire production...
Hold on, I'm working, I got this, okay.
Honestly, this entire production, the whole team like
in studio has been like five people...
...and then everybody working on it behind the scenes
is like three or so.
Compare that to like, the, the thirty-plus people
that work on the really high-quality productions that they do for birthdays and stuff like that.
You know, you get one, you get one...
...one that you get to do a year.
I was going to say 'one free one,' but you really only get to do one, right?
Which is why I'm so glad that we did this together,
and I'm so grateful that it turned out the way that it did.
But, but hold on a sec. Look.
Oh god, my jacket! Oh, jacket!
Look at everybo- look at everyone.
It's CouncilRyS!
This is a bit of a smaller, a smaller little performance area
compared to the others...
...but look at that Gura trident!
Although I will say, lady in the back,
is that supposed to be Gura?
'Cause there are some differences.
I'm sure that you all can...
Not now, not now.
Not now, Mori.
Not now.
But you never know.
I don't really know if that's something she cared very much about, but...
Catching strays, catching strays.
No, but, I look really angry. Hold on, let me...
There. There we go.
Oh man. I hope that my friends who...
are no longer active with us anymore are...
living their best lives out there, and...
doing amazing, cool stuff, wherever they are.
You know?
That's what I want,
more than anything.
That would make me happy.
A lot of those faces around us here too, I really appreciate them.
I'm glad I got to get to know them.
And I'll keep watching them in my own way, in my heart.
Stop getting sentimental!
It's getting later into the stream, so it's happening.
We got to move along, though, we got to move along,
cause there's something that I really...
I really think I need to show you. There's something really cool.
Follow... follow me!
Off we go! We're moving, we're moving on up.
We're going, we're out of here.
Oh, but really quick,
I wanted to mention something, and I think this might be a good place to announce this.
There's...
something... there's a little secret, something-something, below this area.
It's related to Mori.
It's related to Mori, but...
there's a little... a little secret
for Dead Beats to check out
underneath
this stage. Why would you be able to check it out, though, if we didn't see it today?
Well,
that's because the plan is to release
this world, in the next few days,
to you guys!
So that you can hang out here with your friends,
and explore around, and just chill together.
And it'll be so fun! I hope that you guys will...
have a good time with it, and explore, and find little secrets,
like what we found, or what we're finding today.
So, make sure that you get a chance to.
And we'll make sure that you guys know where to access it and find it.
So, that'll be really fun!
Um, let's go, let's go.
Still things I want to show you.
Oh man, how far...
Oh!
You know what?
This is the place over here that...
that I was most interested in running towards.
Come on, come on, come on, let's go, let's go!
We're moving, we're shmoving!
Here we go!
Guys, did any of you guys see this in the distance? The...
the desert.
The desert!
The nerd run. Hey, don't say... that's not true! It's a very cool run.
It's a very cool run I'm doing right now...
No, no, no, am I walking on the water? No, that's totally...
Oh, chat, don't worry, it's just...
No, I'm not... I'm not J-man. No, chat. Wrong, wrong, wrong.
Chigau yo. 'Ame Desert?' Yes!
Yeah.
It looks kind of
gray right now.
But, here, let's take a look.
That's Ame Desert.
That's the Ame Desert over there.
And that big clock?
Do you guys think...
you think there may be something behind the clock?
Cause I want to go find out.
I want to see how far I can... I can dive into this place,
but I get the feeling we might find something nice.
Really quick.
Hold on a sec.
Oh, I'm excited. I'm excited. What are we going to find?
A bus stop? There is a bus stop in the middle of the desert.
I knew it!
It's a dimensional door!
Guys, look!
I found a dimensional door!
Though I kind of had a feeling it would be here, and I may have been told by the powers that be that there was something back here.
But,
shall we go take a look?
Together?
Let me take off this beanie, I'm sick of looking like a rap- It's very cute, though.
I mean, I... The idea was
mine to have the beanie on.
Let's go into space together.
More darkness? No, no, no, no.
Whoa, we're in space!
Is it okay for me to be walking on this floor?
Yep.
I'm not going to die, right?
Hey!
Is this the original bus stop?
This is the original desert bus stop, it feels like.
And... and everything is in the same...
the same kind of lower poly style.
And another bus stop?
And then in here,
something familiar?
Whoa!
HoloMyth...
one year.
Smol...
...Ina timeline.
This side we didn't...
This is the original place.
We've got the Ina room.
I feel like I shouldn't be allowed to be here, but...
...I want to sit down for like a cup of tea.
The original!
Look at that little Takodachi being so good.
And all Ina's paintings for all of us.
Memories...
Crying YAGOO statue? Look at him, look at him cry.
We'll go in there in a second.
And then there's my old room! You guys remember my old room?
Huh?
And the Moon Stage! Wow, from the hell temple, it's like the same...
...the same style and everything. Remember when I did a small concert here?
It's the Mori Cave!
Wow, it was so fun chilling out here with you guys. I know it's kind of older now, and...
...a little worn down, but I miss this old chill spot.
I wonder if we got all of them here, oh my goodness.
We have time to check out all of them?
What's the time looking like? We're going to have to...
...move on pretty soon, but I don't want to! I want to keep looking!
Look! KFP Square!
Oh man, do you guys remember all the fun, like, Easter-themed stuff, or, like...
...spring-themed stuff that used to happen? Was there an egg hunt? I'm pretty sure...
...there was a VR Chat egg hunt, one of them...
...that we did in this kind of place, and all the little games that we did as well.
Kiara did so much fun VR Chat stuff, too,
if I remember correctly... memory serves, and I think it does.
Uh, memory serves correctly.
I feel kind of out of place here being in full color, but...
I feel old, dads! Says chat.
Ah, it's not that long ago. It's only half a decade.
Let's go...
...to...
What we got here?
Oh, I guess that, yeah, there was the Ame desert, and then...
...Gumba's room,
which, we already, we already checked out Atlantis, but look, you can kind of see...
...everything's kind of older and worn out here, and the pillars too...
...are kind of broken, but...
...but I remember it.
I remember what this place used to look like.
Man, it was so fun getting to explore all the different rooms, too.
Uh, I can hear Ride on Time right now.
It's really nostalgic.
Well, I hope that you guys get a chance to enjoy...
...this world, because there was so much love put into it...
...by Seafoam. Thank you so much.
And thank you so much to, to Maylyn as well...
...for working so hard on this. I love it.
I want to do my own exploring later.
And then we can't forget...
You guys, here we are! The original Open Bar!
It's the bar!
Our old bar where we hung out and...
...just chatted the days away.
All the silly, stupid jokes...
...and our small forms.
Everything's kind of decrepit now, but...
...the beginning, right? All the memories.
Movie nights.
We had a lot of fun watch-alongs, didn't we?
Elevator, auditorium...
Remember... Oh my gosh, wait! Hold on!
Happy HoloMyth First Anniversary!
Yeah, four years ago.
Hi, Mom!
Hey, Deadbeats!
Look at how much I've grown.
We've all grown, haven't we?
Everybody was crying because we couldn't meet each other.
And then we did!
Man, half a decade, huh?
We should, we should get out of here before I get too, you know, uh...
...let's...
Funny walk, funny run! Ahaha, so silly!
We got barely any time left, but...
...I'm sure it'll be okay.
One last thing I wanted to show you is this place.
It's the ship!
Sunfish ship!
You guys remember this place, too? Remember our small adventures together?
Oh man, and we looked out here and we saw, we saw Sana was so big.
Yeah.
And then...
...and then, of course, our Captain was driving here.
...adventures.
The sunfish!
Maybe I should take this baby on a joyride.
I'm sure Ame wouldn't mind.
I'm thinking about it, though.
Especially after coming back here.
Well, I think we should
quick-transport back to the desert, guys,
since we don't have much time left.
I have teleport abilities, though.
All I have to do is summon my persona. Okay, here we go.
But I hope you guys get a chance to
check this place out in more detail, you know?
That would make me really happy.
Ah! We're back!
Because I feel like after all we've looked at so far,
and all the memories that we've experienced,
there's a special song that I want to sing here.
But I have the feeling I already sang it.
Well then,
shall we remember?
Let's go.
Castle made of thorns, moon that rose in crimson
Grab for something more, all I get is distance
Driving roadless, feels like the end of a life
Running through those nights
All I saw were curses stuck here unalive
Floating on the surface, still and shallow
Probably left to rot, I'm sinking
So close to...
Giving up, giving out, giving in
Could I still live again, live again, live again?
But what's the point in fighting when nothing lasts at all?
On your last day
Standing here alone with you, I found my vision was
Way off, way off, yeah
Now I can't wake up, wake up, yeah
Don't tell me it's over, it must be...
Is it gonna be just me left behind?
Me and my mind,
forever wasting time
Back then there was nothing left to lose
Back then every night was wine and blues
That's when every pen I tried to use ended up leaking my weakness and bled through
All in, but still a little mistaken
Faking like I knew the risk taken
Wakin' up, every night pacing
Was it all a waste then? Am I worth replacing?
Locked down deep in my soul is what I really want to shout
Now, out of control, but I still hold it inside
And now there's nowhere to hide, you wanna know if I'm fine
Well, at least nobody's died
so close to...
Giving up, giving out, giving in
Could I still live again, live again, live again?
But what's the point in fighting when nothing lasts at all?
On your last day
Standing here alone with you, I found my vision was
Way off, way off, yeah
Now I can't wake up, wake up, yeah
Don't tell me it's over, it must be...
Is it gonna be just me left behind?
Me and my mind,
forever...
Every now and then reality creeps in
Every now and then I glance over the deep end
You'll live on, still, so when I'm not around
Remember me...
Remember what we found...
On our last day
Standing here alone 'cause nothing lasts forever
Wake up, wake up, yeah
No, I can't wake up, wake up, yeah
No... It's not over, it can't be
Is it gonna be just me left behind?
Is this goodbye?
On my last day
Doesn't matter where or when I swear I'll find us
A way out, way out, yeah
So let things play out, play out, yeah
'Cause I know some dreams just can't come true
But I wanna see you again sometime
That song in my heart, it kept me alive
Hey there, Dead Beats.
Hey there.
It's me.
It's okay to be sad.
It's okay
to miss the people who changed our lives
if they aren't here anymore.
I think...
it's okay.
But as long as we have memories, right?
Um, then I think...
maybe,
just maybe,
it'll be okay, even if we never truly move on.
I'm happy that we have memories,
right?
And to never, never forget
all the stuff that we did together.
'Cause we did some really amazing stuff, don't you guys think?
I think we did.
And I don't want to forget any of that, 'cause,
like I said, I don't really have any plans to get going anytime soon.
But, I guess the way that I feel about it is...
I'd like to keep remembering all those people and things that we did fondly,
regardless of anything.
Even through the years and though they may pass by,
and even when the wounds aren't fresh anymore,
I still...
I still want to remember.
I know it's hard to move forward sometimes when
the things that we love and care about are still behind us,
right?
Stuck in the past, but...
I'm gonna be here to make you smile no matter what.
Right now, there's still stuff I want to do,
you know?
And yeah, that's a good point! Good memories, they should make you sad, because...
...because that means they were truly good.
We did a lot of really good stuff, don't you guys think?
Well, I'm glad that I sang that here with Ina.
I'm really glad.
But there's still some people that I haven't sung with,
so let's head to the final area, shall we?
What if I just... bam! Teleported myself there,
and used my crazy powers of... oh, my waist is broken.
That's okay. No, it's fine. All good, all good.
I probably just need to T-pose real quick.
Hey, watch this.
Watch my sick T-pose.
Hang on.
I'm already good at this.
I've become a pro at VR Chat in just this short time.
There we go. Fixed.
All right. Time to summon my persona and head to the final area!
Oh!
Oof, we're here.
We're here. Oh,
where did my camera go?
I lost it. Is it hiding...
Is it behind me?
Oh, I found it!
There you are.
I found you.
Um, this is one of my favorite areas, I think.
You guys...
You guys, look! What is this? Green fields?
Oh, there's one of those camera thingies. Hang on, okay.
Uh, check this out.
Whoa!
It's too beautiful!
Can you guys imagine hanging out with your friends here?
Wouldn't that be so awesome?
Um, I'm running up that hill.
I'm running up the hill.
Oh my gosh!
Hey...
Wait a minute. What's this?
Was Ina painting something here? I didn't know about that.
Hey... I mean, it is a really nice scenery to paint, I suppose.
Yeah, I guess it makes sense.
I'd want to paint here.
So expansive... oh, sorry, wrong...
that's okay, doesn't matter.
Um, so surreal and tranquil.
I guess this is a good place to tell you guys the news about a special thing that gets released
for anniversary, especially. Do you guys know what it is? Are we gonna run the clip?
I think we're gonna run the clip!
All right, guys. We have merchandise, so...
I created a little commercial,
before we get to singing here. Run it, Staff-san!
Ahem! Minasan, it's been five long years together, but we've done it!
We made it to year five together, and...
...while the future's looking pretty crazy and eventful,
let's take a little time to celebrate the story thus far, shall we?
And what better way to do that than with every Holo's bread and butter,
the bane of every Dead Beat's wallet...
...its existence!
That's right, everybody. It's time for...
...premium goods, goods, goods, goods!
Yeah, premium goods time.
You guys, you guys know what time it is.
You get ready for it every year, right?
Yeah, you guys know how I like to release merch
that's more on the fashionable side than practical, but...
...I think there are a few things that you guys are gonna love here.
And remember, if you grab it quick and manage to cop the premium limited set,
you'll get a hand-signed postcard from me!
Ari-ari-arigatou!
But, like always, supplies are extremely...
are limited so don't miss out, okay?
Okay? Okay.
First we got a poster.
I mean, you guys expect posters by now I think.
You guys are used to posters from me.
As every good deadbeat knows Mori Calliope is a poster fan, and Mori Calliope fans are fans of posters!
As every good Dead Beat knows, Mori Calliope is a poster fan, and Mori Calliope fans are fans of posters!
I see your rooms. I know.
Not like in a creepy way or anything.
This one's a bit smaller than the usual huge posters that I always do for these merch drops, but...
it's to help with the shipping cost this year.
...it's to help with the shipping costs this year.
I don't know, we'll see. Crossing my fingers, but no guarantees.
Throw it into your cart and see what happens, I guess.
I went for an Underworld Live Show concert poster as a concept here, and...
my very own Yuki-san mama created something fun and energetic for the occasion.
So let's reminisce on the amazing shows that we've gotten to experience together
with this big-sized poster! Yeah yeah!
Next up, oh man, this one is big!
One of my favorite apparel artists, Crisalys, has graced
this humble black t-shirt with a high quality and subtle design
...this humble black T-shirt with a high-quality and subtle design...
of your Mori dressed in Grimoire attire
playing her bass, probably a little badly, in an antique shop!
It's the type of shirt where you'll probably get, you know, compliments from fellow quirky folks
but the average bystander, like, wouldn't look twice at you kind of deal.
I don't know. Again, I can't guarantee exactly what's going to happen.
Anyway, you might find Dead Beats out in the wild, too, so that's fun.
It's just the kind of shirt that subtly expresses your love for Mori Calliope
without being too, you know, in your face, right?
And the design is so so so good!
I own like five shirts by Crisalys, now I'm about to own six.
Anyway, don't miss out.
Next up, it's a Grimoire plushie!
Take her everywhere with you, that seems to be all the rage these days, right?
And if you give her a squeeze, she says something.
I don't know what yet, but maybe we'll all be a little surprised.
She's got such a cute and huggable design.
I'm sure she'll make fast friends with your other plushies.
Especially, uh, that weird cat, you know.
Maybe you can dress her up and put her in a plastic purse for a day out.
Just, just have fun, I don't know, be whimsical, whatever you want to do.
Finally, it's a concert and live show staple
a casual wristband!
Show your support for your Mori in your everyday life
or at a local show, even if, you know, I'm not the one playing.
Something easy to slip on and fun to rock out with.
I want to see all of you guys wearing them at my future shows, okay?
And there's a voice pack, too!
Ah, "Mori Takes a Break"?
Eh? What kind of title is that?
It sounds like some fanfiction to me, but, you know, give, give it a listen, I guess.
Japanese and English voice available.
日本語もあります！
Also available in Japanese!
Grab the full set and you will get a foil duplicated stamp on a special postcard.
Grab the full set and you will get a foil-duplicated stamp on a special postcard.
Be really fast and get your hands on that limited edition set
and you might just get your hands on a handwritten autograph from Mori Calliope.
Actually, it's not that you might. You will.
You will get a handwritten autograph from Mori Calliope, if you're fast enough.
We always do gold, though, so how about I sign it with an extra special pink pen?
We always do gold, though, so how about I sign it with an extra-special pink pen?
I don't know, we'll have to see if they let me. Look forward to it!
And again, these are limited to a certain amount.
So, if you want to grab a real autograph from your Mori, do not miss out on this chance.
The sales period will run for about a month
so get your premium goods ASAP, okay?
It's like a full-on concert hall over here
between poster, t-shirt, squeezable mini Mori, and wristband.
Get ready for lots more shows together, Dead Beats.
And thanks for the unforgettable five years! Mwah!
I wonder, how much further can we go together?
I want to see!
Hello!
Thank you so much, everybody. I hope that you guys enjoy the goods.
Please look forward to receiving them. They're very cool.
I'm super excited with how they turned out. Um, so make sure that you don't miss it.
I think the shop will open in about six minutes.
You'll be able to pre-order your merch and get the limited, if you're
if you're quick. You got to be quick
because they, they do have a limited number.
Um, but yeah, please enjoy.
And thank you always for supporting me so much.
There will be a members-only encore after this
featuring a few more songs, and just getting to chat with my members, which I'm excited about.
Um, so please look forward to that.
And there's a new song! I should look a little happier about that. There's a new song coming out!
Um, and I haven't really given any hints about what kind of song it is.
People are like, "Oh, it's going to be so emotional, this looks like an emotional song."
But knowing what the song is makes me laugh really hard
because it's actually a lot simpler than you think.
But, something about my early music is that
man, I was so honest, you know?
And so, I wanted to write a song
that not just me, myself, I as a person could relate to, but anyone
anyone who has an oshi could relate to.
And so...
I hope that you will enjoy it, because
it feels like an older Mori song, while also being a newer Mori song.
It's hard to explain, but I guess you'll just have to watch it and see.
The MV is really cute, so we'll watch that premiere together, too.
So don't go anywhere after the credits.
Um, please look forward to it.
New song, new song, stream it a lot
Watch it lots, and, um, share it around. I don't know, if you want, if you like it.
Um, but I still have one last song memory to replay in my mind here, in this beautiful area.
So shall we run it? The last song of today.
Thank you so much, Dead Beats.
Catch you on the flip side. There might be an after-credit scene. Let's go!
Scuffed Up Age
[Title: Scuffed Up Age]
lost in thoughts of frosted frame of mind
Lost in thoughts of a frosted frame of mind,
honest to god, it’s just not our time
Honest to God, it's just not our time.
promises flawed by cosmic design
これくらいどうってことない
This much is really nothing,
でも涙の跡は消せない
but the trace of tears can't be erased.
coming of age, the stage doesn’t light up
Coming of age, the stage doesn't light up.
just right away, they told us it might ’ve
Just right away, they told us it might've.
夢はもう諦めます
I will give up on my dreams now.
this cynical mind says “why ’d you try ?”
This cynical mind says, "Why'd you try?"
why not give up and play the bad guy ?
Why not give up and play the bad guy?
分かってるとさ
I know that already.
運命が波立てながら あなた飲もうとするのなら
If fate stirs up waves and tries to swallow you,
崩れ落ちそうな身体 抱きしめるから
I will embrace your crumbling body.
we choose to know
the struggles of this scuffed up age we ’re living in
the struggles of this scuffed up age we're living in.
腐ったクズの日々だけど
Even if these are rotten, garbage days,
この夜明け could seem a lot like “ not your day ”
this dawn could seem a lot like "not your day."
それでもあなたを捨ててしまわないで
But even so, please don't cast yourself away.
can’t find a reason to stay
Can't find a reason to stay,
some busted world led astray
once trusted, left to decay
we choose to go on anyway.
lost in thoughts of always changing pace
Lost in thoughts of an always-changing pace,
allies and friends hiding more than one face
not really surprising, why are you compromising ?
Not really surprising, why are you compromising?
the sun is rising a new horizon
with friendships lacking lies and
the knives in your back, so what are you prioritizing ?
the knives in your back, so what are you prioritizing?
you aren’t sick of crying ? see, i don’t buy it.
You aren't sick of crying? See, I don't buy it,
but here we are, hanging on, fighting strong despite it.
“ 儚い ” じゃ表し 切れない
"Fleeting" doesn't fully express it,
もう目を閉じて しまいたい くらいの世界
a world where I just want to close my eyes.
this cynical mind says “why ’d you try ?”
This cynical mind says, "Why'd you try?"
“ why not give up and play the bad guy ? ”
"Why not give up and play the bad guy?"
分からないんだ
I don't know anymore.
埃まみれの街で あなたのため息の影
In this dust-covered town, the shadow of your sigh...
私の微かな火で 照らしたいだけ
I just want to light it up with my faint flame.
we choose to know
the struggles of this scuffed up age we ’re giving in
the struggles of this scuffed up age we're giving in.
土砂に汚れて be real, it hurts to grow
Covered in mud, be real, it hurts to grow.
believing in a world of hate is overrated
まあ、でもあなたは美しいのだから
Well, but you are beautiful, after all,
must be something surreal
so it must be something surreal.
an endless dream we can’t heal
An endless dream we can't heal,
this rusted world wound up real
still wanna love the way it feels.
I still want to love the way it feels.
late nights, the city feels dead, sure, but like…
Late nights, the city feels dead, sure, but like...
the lights and sights and sounds are treasures.
...the lights, sights, and sounds are treasures.
こんな世界に抗って歩く力なんて
The strength to walk resisting such a world,
私にはないけど
I don't have it in me, but...
face up, this world can’t kill that inner spark
Face up, this world can't kill that inner spark.
why don’t we turn this scuffed up page we ’re writing in
Why don't we turn this scuffed up page we're writing in?
こんな世界じゃ be real, i think we know
In this world, be real, I think we know.
この夜明け is rarely fair, decide your fate
This dawn is rarely fair, decide your fate,
it ’s your life あなたを捨ててしまわないで
it's your life, please don't cast yourself away.
tomorrow ’s a brand new day
Tomorrow's a brand new day,
like all those optimists say
but the truth is rather ruthless, it might be rain
the question is, will you bear that pain ?
The question is, will you bear that pain?
what ’s your reason to stay ?
What's your reason to stay?
this shining world led astray
won’t leave it all to decay
won't leave it all to decay,
i choose to love it anyway.
We choose to know
the struggles of this scuffed up age we live in
so, don't give in
What are you still doing here? The show is over.
Go watch the music video!
Thank you, Yulice and nanoless, for the 3D!
Bye!
Thank you all for 5 incredibly strange, wonderful, whimsical, at times painful but so, so special years as your Mori.
[Letter] Thank you all for 5 incredibly strange, wonderful, whimsical, at times painful but so, so special years as your Mori.
There are so many more views I want to see, but for now just know how thankful I am that I get to be your Pink woman. Always.
We laughed. We cried. We cringed. And we'll do it again, dammit!!
Love, Calliope